<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cooke Recipe</string>

    <string name="recipe_1">Amish Sugar Cookies</string>
    <string name="recipe_2">Vanilla Wafer Cookies</string>
    <string name="recipe_3">Semisweet Chocolate Pinwheel Cookies</string>
    <string name="recipe_4">White Chocolate Macadamia Nut Cookies</string>
    <string name="recipe_5">Church Window Cookies</string>
    <string name="recipe_6">Loaded-Up Pretzel Cookies</string>
    <string name="recipe_7">Dipped Peanut Butter Sandwich Cookies</string>
    <string name="recipe_8">Easy Oatmeal Cream Pies</string>
    <string name="recipe_9">Mini Peanut Butter Sandwich Cookies</string>
    <string name="recipe_10">Lemon Snowflakes</string>
    <string name="recipe_11">Frosted Butter Cutout Cookies</string>
    <string name="recipe_12">Pecan Sandies</string>
    <string name="recipe_13">Homemade Chocolate Shortbread</string>
    <string name="recipe_14">Cream Wafers</string>
    <string name="recipe_15">Chocolate Butterscotch Haystacks</string>
    <string name="recipe_16">Lemon Rosemary Butter Cookies</string>
    <string name="recipe_17">Old-Fashioned Gingersnaps</string>
    <string name="recipe_18">Ginger Creme Sandwich Cookies</string>
    <string name="recipe_19">Snicker doodle Crisps</string>
    <string name="recipe_20">Lavender Cookies</string>
    <string name="recipe_21">Cherry Cheese Windmills</string>
    <string name="recipe_22">Pumpkin Whoopie Pies</string>
    <string name="recipe_23">Italian Sprinkle Cookies</string>
    <string name="recipe_24">Chocolate-Covered Cherry Thumbprints</string>
    <string name="recipe_25">Toffee Almond Sandies</string>
    <string name="recipe_26">Lemon Curd Cookies</string>
    <string name="recipe_27">Cran-Orange Icebox Cookies</string>

    <string name="recipe_1_description">These easy to-make cookies simply melt in your mouth! I\'ve passed this recipe around to many friends. After I gave it to my sister, she entered the cookies in a local fair and won the best of show prize! Try using different flavored extracts in place of the vanilla for a change of taste.</string>
    <string name="recipe_2_description">These buttery cookies bake up chewy and crispy at the same time. Sprinkle these vanilla wafers with colored sugar or leave them as-is. Their simplicity is beauty enough! —Edith MacBeath, Gaines, Pennsylvania</string>
    <string name="recipe_3_description">Chocolate and vanilla provide a delightful contrast in their flavor and appearance. —Nancy Arevalo, Brookfield, Wisconsin!</string>
    <string name="recipe_4_description">Hawaiian nuts and melty morsels make a fantastic combination in these buttery white chocolate macadamia nut cookies. —Cathy Lennon, Newport, Tennessee!</string>
    <string name="recipe_5_description">These church window cookies are a hit with kids—the little ones just love the colored marshmallows! —Emmilie Gaston, Wabash, Indiana!</string>
    <string name="recipe_6_description">Coconut, M M’s and salty, crunchy pretzels make these loaded cookies unlike any you’ve ever tasted—or resisted. —Jackie Ruckwardt, Cottage Grove, Oregon!</string>
    <string name="recipe_7_description">You\'ll love to give tins of these chocolate-coated cookies to your lucky friends. The shortcut holiday recipe is almost too simple to believe! Here\'s how to make peanut butter cookies without eggs. —Jackie Howell, Gordo, Alabama!</string>
    <string name="recipe_8_description">These easy cookies use only five ingredients and taste very similar to a store-bought cookie. Of course, everything\'s better from your own kitchen! —Crystal Schlueter, Northglenn, Colorado!</string>
       <string name="recipe_9_description">Peanut butter lovers go nuts for these rich little sandwich cookies. On a hot day, sandwich ice cream between the cookies instead of frosting. It cools you right down. —Keri Wolfe, Nappanee, Indiana!</string>
       <string name="recipe_10_description">You\'ll need just four ingredients to make these delightful lemon snowflake cookies. Confectioners’ sugar highlights the cracked tops to give them their snowflake appearance. —Linda Barry, Dianna, Texas!</string>
       <string name="recipe_11_description">I have fond memories of baking and frosting these cutout cookies with my mom. Now I carry on the tradition with my kids. It\'s a messy but fun day! —Sandy Nace, Greensburg, Kansas!</string>
          <string name="recipe_12_description">These pecan sandies are a deliciously crispy treat. The recipe is very easy to follow and you can make it in no time. —Sarah DeHart, Huntington, Indiana!</string>
          <string name="recipe_13_description"> This recipe has been in my files for a long time…probably from when I first learned to bake. Any chocolate lover will like these melt-in-your-mouth cookies. I make them year-round with variations. They\'re even richer with a thin coat of icing or as a sandwich cookie with frosting in the middle. —Sarah Bueckert, Austin, Manitoba! </string>
        <string name="recipe_14_description">My sons used to help me make these cookies, and now my oldest granddaughter helps. When the smaller grandchildren are home, they help, too. The cute little sandwich cookies are tender, buttery and melt-in-your-mouth good! —Linda Clinkenbeard, Vincennes, Indiana!</string>
        <string name="recipe_15_description">My grandmother used to make this haystacks recipe to give to my cousin Vonnie and me when our parents didn\'t want us to have any more sweets. —Christine Schwester, Divide, Colorado!</string>
        <string name="recipe_16_description">Cooling lemon and aromatic rosemary make these butter cookies stand out at the holidays. I use them to punch up the cookie trays for potlucks or as gifts.—Elizabeth Hokanson, Arborg, Manitoba!</string>
        <string name="recipe_17_description">I discovered this recipe many years ago, and it\'s been a favorite among our family and friends ever since. Gingersnaps are timeless—a classic holiday cookie that\'s welcome year-round. —Francis Stoops, Stoneboro, Pennsylvania!</string>
        <string name="recipe_18_description">With a lemony filling, these spiced cookies go over big because they have old-fashioned, comfort-food appeal. Your party guests will snatch them up! - Carol Walston, Granbury, Texas!</string>
        <string name="recipe_19_description">This classic cookie from New England can be made two ways: soft or crunchy. My happy version with cinnamon, ginger and nutmeg is crispy to perfection. —Jenni Sharp, Milwaukee, Wisconsin!</string>
         <string name="recipe_20_description">I am a wedding and event planner and one of my brides served these unusual cookies at her reception, so I had to have this lavender butter cookies recipe. You can guess what her wedding color was! —Glenna Tooman, Boise, Idaho!</string>
         <string name="recipe_21_description">These pretty cookies look fancy, but they are really not much work. They\'re perfect for any occasion. —Helen McGibbon, Downers Grove, Illinois</string>
       <string name="recipe_22_description">My kids start begging me for these cakelike sandwich cookies as soon as autumn arrives. I haven\'t met a person yet who doesn\'t like these fun treats. —Deb Stuber, Carlisle, Pennsylvania</string>
     <string name="recipe_23_description">Of all the Italian cookie recipes I make, this is my favorite. These sprinkle cookies take some time, but, believe me, they are well worth it! My husband and I used to operate an Italian American restaurant, and this recipe goes back generations. Gloria Cracchiolo, Newburgh, New York</string>
     <string name="recipe_24_description">When I dig out my best cookie recipes, I’m reminded of baking with my children when they were little. These thumbprints with cherries elicit such sweet memories. –Deborah Puette, Lilburn, Georgia</string>
     <string name="recipe_25_description">These crispy classics are loaded with crunchy chopped toffee and almonds, so there\'s no doubt as to why they\'re my husband\'s favorite cookie. I used to bake them in large batches when our four sons still lived at home. Now I whip them up for the grandchildren! —Alice Kahnk, Kennard, Nebraska</string> -->
    <string name="recipe_26_description">I\'ve made these cookies for years. I like to give them out to family and friends. —Carole Vogel, Allison Park, Pennsylvania</string>
    <string name="recipe_27_description">These are among my family\'s favorite cookies around Christmas. The cran-orange flavor makes them special. —Nancy Rollag, Kewaskum, Wisconsin</string>

    <string name="day_1">Day 1</string>
    <string name="day_2">Day 2</string>
    <string name="day_3">Day 3</string>
    <string name="day_4">Day 4</string>
    <string name="day_5">Day 5</string>
    <string name="day_6">Day 6</string>
    <string name="day_7">Day 7</string>
    <string name="day_8">Day 8</string>
    <string name="day_9">Day 9</string>
    <string name="day_10">Day 10</string>
    <string name="day_11">Day 11</string>
    <string name="day_12">Day 12</string>
    <string name="day_13">Day 13</string>
    <string name="day_14">Day 14</string>
    <string name="day_15">Day 15</string>
    <string name="day_16">Day 16</string>
    <string name="day_17">Day 17</string>
    <string name="day_18">Day 18</string>
    <string name="day_19">Day 19</string>
    <string name="day_20">Day 20</string>
    <string name="day_21">Day 21</string>
    <string name="day_22">Day 22</string>
    <string name="day_23">Day 23</string>
    <string name="day_24">Day 24</string>
    <string name="day_25">Day 25</string>
    <string name="day_26">Day 26</string>
    <string name="day_27">Day 27</string>


</resources>
